New Account Generic:
Address: K2LJBS6MO5E7QW5IMHJWUBLKLODZNWXRPI5HEZIYFMKTHBMTIVO7L7J3UA
Mnemonic: funny wheat capable carbon tip winner almost captain sock between shaft unlock endless found purchase amount mercy foam parent coffee timber deposit inmate absorb harsh
--------------------------------------------------
Please fund this account using the Algorand Testnet Dispenser: https://lora.algokit.io/testnet/faucet
